{
    "id": "9664eaa0b285430a881a42d0eb94efee",
    "title": "Past Simple And Past Perfect Tense Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "By the time the fire fighters ……………., the fire ……………… many huts.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "arrived, destroyed",
                "had arrived, destroyed",
                "arrived, had destroyed"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "95eb5c91a92d426a96a7e176f614ac13"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was not …………….. to write the exam, because he ……………….. his hall ticket.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "permitted, did not bring",
                "permitted, had not brought",
                "permitted, has not brought"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "589e3a6f0aa04088b0730a0e967ca1ee"
        },
        {
            "question": "Long before the chief guest ………………., the invitees  …………….. .",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "had arrived, had assembled",
                "arrived, assembled",
                "arrived, had assembled"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f765bc20e6f543fea015336f537e0fc9"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish you …………….. your application in time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sent",
                "have sent",
                "had sent"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "8f76f74ec0b941c48b25b59fdc40373b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The police …………… the thief. They ……………. for him for two months.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "caught, looked",
                "had caught, had been looking",
                "caught, had been looking"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "388392bf688d4ee8b1c1eadc01df6ef8"
        },
        {
            "question": "If they ………………. the Principal, he would have helped them.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "met",
                "have met",
                "had met"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "912c2ce6c513428dbd69133796659950"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………….. to him, as I ………………… to him formally.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have not spoken, was not introduced",
                "did not speak, was not introduced",
                "had not spoken, was not introduced"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "af737c8f0ab34be78cae672c0bbf5c28"
        },
        {
            "question": "By the time we ………….. the station, the train  …………… .",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "had reached, had left",
                "reached, left",
                "reached, had left"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "dbf5ffd2b4ad414dbdf95a47f9d9c26d"
        },
        {
            "question": "If Balu ………….. the secretary earlier, he …………… him a job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "see, would give",
                "saw, would have given",
                "had seen, would have given"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a15f7bcfd40640d0ac8f5e07dacc8743"
        },
        {
            "question": "If Raju ……………. in our team, we ……………. .",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "were, would win",
                "were, would have won",
                "were, will win"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "12360bcd7ca440e1bfdc26193f0c4515"
        }
    ]
}